westbyte.com 2010-06-22

# WestByte | Privacy

**WestByte Privacy Practices**  
This statement discloses the privacy practices for the WestByte Web site. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to WestByte at: .

**Personal Information**  
At WestByte we respect your right to privacy and we understand that, as a visitor to westbyte.com, you prefer to control your own personal information and preferences. For this reason, we may ask you to register or to provide personal information and preferences when you visit certain areas of westbyte.com, download free software, request information, or subscribe to WestByte newsletter.

We will not share, sell, or otherwise distribute the financial or personal information of our customers or those who otherwise provide personal information to sample our products, to any other organizations in any way other than what is disclosed in this document.

**Orders**  
To provide you with high quality purchasing experience in a secure environment we have partnered with two leading international software registration services: RegSoft and ShareIt. Both of these companies have been specializing in secure online credit card payments for a number of years. You can find additional information about our registrators privacy policies at [Element 5 AG (ShareIt!) Privacy](http://www.element5.com/privacy.html) and [RegSoft Privacy statement](http://www.regsoft.com/privacy%20statement.shtml).

**Cookies**  
There are various technologies, including one called "cookies", which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. WestByte uses the data collected from website visitor cookies in aggregate form only and does not collect any personally identifiable information. Use of this information helps us better understand what users are seeking and learning at our website(s) and helps us identify potential navigation issues.  

**Forums**  
The information gathered for the WestByte User Forums is completely voluntary. A user need only enter a name and email address. Whether or not this information is displayed on the website is up to the user. This simply provides a means to interact with other Forum Users. This information is not required by WestByte. Any information posted to a Users Forum is considered in the public domain.

**Links**  
In some areas of the website, WestByte may choose to link to another website. We cannot be responsible for any of the content on these external sites. We are also not responsible for the privacy policies in place on that site.

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices, you can contact us at: .
